Guide to the Harry W. Cox Papers, 1948-1977 (bulk 1962-1976)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Administrative Records, 1948-1977
  - Letter to Price Waterhouse and Company concerning accounting, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Letter from Raphaelian Rug Co., Inc. regarding shipping and care of a Persian Keshan silk rug, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding a Spanish tapestry. Several documents are in Spanish with English translation, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Offer to Doris Duke to purchase tract of land in Hillsborough. Doris Duke declined, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence regarding upkeep of Holt family plot at Rose Hill Cemetery, Macon, GA, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence regarding gifts of stock to the Self-Realization Fellowship Church from Doris Duke, 1970–1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Documents pertaining to investment and the eventual failure of the Seventrees Holster company, 1968-1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence concerning the Estate of Sydney Shaw, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence regarding gift of $1,000 to Somerset Hospital from Doris Duke, 1970–1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Thank you letter from Emmett Hoffmann acknowledging $25 gift to St. Labre Indian School, Ashland, MN, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Reissue of check for libraries of Florida State University and Florida A&M, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Letter acknowledging gift of $1,000 to Syvilla Fort Phillips Fund from Doris Duke, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence regarding Doris Duke's investment in the London production of GYPSY via the Sing Out Company, 1973–1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Letter requesting fact-checking of Doris Duke biographical information for Town & Country Magazine, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence regarding dispute of charges for parcel of two magnetic tapes. Also includes correspondence with Clover Enterprises, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Census data for Doris Duke’s various foundations, 1972–1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence regarding gift of stock valued $50,000 to the University of Arizona in support for the Indian Oral History Program, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence regarding support for the Indian Oral History Program at the University of Florida, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence regarding continued support of the Duke Indian Oral History Program at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 1970–1971 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence regarding gift of $17,000 to the University of Massachusetts from Doris Duke, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence regarding support of the Duke Indian Oral History Program at the University of New Mexico, 1970–1971 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence regarding continued support of the Duke Indian Oral History Program at the University of Oklahoma, 1970–1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence regarding grant of $50,000 to the University of South Dakota, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence regarding gift of stock to Western History Center, Indian Oral History Project at the University of Utah, 1970–1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Bill for evaluation of jewelry and request for appraisal of 1971 donation to the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Letter regarding gift of 51.597 acres in Hillsborough to the Veterans Administration, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence regarding gift of $25,000 for library at Wofford College from Doris Duke, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to Yves Saint Laurent regarding repair of belt, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Letters concerning Doris Duke's role as an Albert Gallatin Fellow in selecting the winner of the Albert Gallatin Medal, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers and notes given to Harry W. Cox upon C.E. Allcock’s retirement. Includes several documents about Duke Farms, explanations of Doris Duke’s Balance Sheet from 1959, and Doris Duke’s Gross Income from 1956-1965, 1927-1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Report from Irene Calvet, Head of Households, to Doris Duke regarding Newport residence, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence regarding the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1969–1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Letters handled by Elise Cooper for Doris Duke. Topics include invitations, billing issues, correspondence with Christie’s auction house, and annual dues for memberships, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Elise Cooper’s (Secretary) to Doris Duke regarding both business and personal matters, 1969–1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Confirmation of checks from Morgan Guaranty to Etelvina Ramirez, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Inquiry concerning Doris Duke donations from 1934–1971, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence regarding give to Luis Crespo from Doris Duke, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from Harry W. Cox to Doris Duke concerning a variety of accounting topics, 1969–1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence regarding contract work for roofing, flashing, and masonry at Rough Point, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Political donations for which Doris Duke wished to remain anonymous, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to and from Harry Cox on a variety of topics including permission for Vallance to bid on portrait of Napoleon and 1969 Capital Gains and Losses, 1969–1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence regarding the deed to Prescott Farm for Newport Restoration Foundation, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to and from John Gomez regarding monetary gift upon retirement, notice of infraction, and public tours of Shangri La, 1967–1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence concerning Falcon Lair credit cards, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence concerning loans made by Doris Duke, 1964–1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence relating to loan to Mr. and Mrs. John M. Barber by Doris Duke, 1963–1977 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence relating to loan to Ralph Bergstresser by Doris Duke, 1967–1973 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence and related financial documents relating to loan to Alvin D. Banks by Doris Duke, 1963–1968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence and related financial documents relating to loan to Robert G. Banks by Doris Duke, 1969–1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and related financial documents relating to loans to Angier B. Duke and Anthony D. Duke by Doris Duke, 1970–1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence relating to loan to Eleanor Johnson by Doris Duke, 1956–1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence relating to loan to Sam and Anita Kahanamoku by Doris Duke, 1964–1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence relating to loan to Ian R. Tucker by Doris Duke, 1972–1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence concerning Walker P., Inman, Jr. including closing of various store accounts, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Letter regarding possible donation to the Newport Corps of the Salvation Army, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence regarding insurance payments and funding to cover costs incurred by Anita Kahanamoku for her husband Sam's passing, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Thank you letter for photograph of Walker Inman, Jr. with his biology master, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and notes from Jeanne Liccardo to Doris Duke on a variety of topics including travel, financial, goods, and services, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from Honolulu staff concerning a variety of administrative related topics such as architect's plans, repairs, and notary information, 1970-1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from Germaine Mourlanne regarding monthly checks. Also includes a postcard addressed to Elise Cooper, secretary to Doris Duke, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Unsolicted correspondence to Doris Duke, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Thank you telegram from Doris Duke to Mrs. Michael Cunningham Reid, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence concerning check for $2,000 to assist with medical expenses of Cesar Rubirosa (older brother of Porfirio Rubirosa), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Parke-Bernet sales memorandum, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Unsolicited offers to sell items to SEAAC, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from A.D. Searles to Doris Duke requesting approval of payment to A.B. Kahanamoku. Includes letter to Greenspoon notifying of letter from Tashjian, 1973–1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Cancellation of check to Mattie Holt Huffman on her passing, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence notifying continued legal representation of Duke Power Company, Trustees of The Duke Endowment and the Doris Duke Trust after dissolution of Perkins, Daniels & McCormick, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Thank you letter from St. Augustin’s Social Action Committee for efforts of Newport Restoration Foundation, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence covering the daily operation of The Animal Medical Center. Dr. Tashjian is a correspondent, receiver, or subject, 1970-1973 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence covering the daily operation of The Animal Medical Center. Dr. Tashjian is a correspondent, receiver, or subject, 1970-1973 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Thank you and inquiry into availability of works by Maurice Rocco and Mary Lou Williams, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Unsolicited and denied business proposals and interview request, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum concerning tax code changes for charitable foundations, 1964–1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Letter to Dr. Tashjian concerning IRS classification, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Letter concerning Doris Duke daily planner kept for tax purposes, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Documents pertaining to California taxes. Includes payments made in connection with musical activities in California, 1948–1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Financial and tax documents for Rough Point. Includes memorandum of appraisal and a newspaper clipping regarding assessment, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Drafts of a contract for Clover Records to finance a 30-minute television documentary based upon Tahiti, 1967 and undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Legal documents for DORIDE Corporation, Inc., 1969–1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence regarding Duchess property, Somerville, N.J., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and release of escrow monies for Anthony D. Duke and Angier B. Duke, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Civil action considering the defendants involved in the income beneficiary of James B. Duke, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence concerning legal use of Duke family name. A nearby (N.J.) restaurant adopted the name "Duke Farms Inn", 1970,1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and other legal documents dissolving Duke Farms Foundation, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and substantiation of Duke Farms taxes, 1970–1973 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and substantiation of Duke Farms taxes, 1970–1973 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Federal income tax for Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc., 1958-1971 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Federal income tax for Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc., 1958-1971 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, letters, and substantiation of taxes for the Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. for the period 1970–1972, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Documents originating outside of FAS International concerning Common Stock Class Action, 1968-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence concerning licensing of guns at Duke Farms, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and related documents regarding litigation of Newport Restoration Foundation and Ford Property Improvements, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Letter concerning using General John Colter for First National City Bank transactions, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Documents concerning the lease of Greenfield Plantation to the Georgetown Steel Corporation, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Will of Georgia Inman, Section 1 of 5-Account of Proceedings & Part I, 1958 (1 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Will of Georgia Inman, Sections 2 & 3 of 5-Parts II and III, 1958 (2 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Will of Georgia Inman, Section 4 of 5-Part IV, 1958 (3 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Will of Georgia Inman, Section 5 of 5-Part V, 1958 (4 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence concerning a lawsuit brought forth by John Gomez concerning overpayment of funds to Abe Poepoe, 1965-1976 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence concerning a lawsuit brought forth by John Gomez concerning overpayment of funds to Abe Poepoe, 1965-1976 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Charter of Greenfield Executive Conference Corporation, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hillsborough tax bills, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence concerning Hillsborough taxes. Includes Duke Gardens Foundation tax dispute, 1969–1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence concerning insurance policies for various Duke entities including Duke Farms, SEAAC, and the Near East Dance Foundation, 1969-1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence regarding medical and disability insurance, 1964–1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Letters received by or copied to Harry Cox on various topics including taxes, Duke employees, litigation, investment proposals, bank balances, and stock advice, 1968-1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Letter regarding settlement of the Martin claim, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence regarding finances and insurance for the Near East Dance Foundation, Inc., 1971–1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Official documents for the Near East Dance Foundation, including Certificate of Incorporation, By-laws, application for authority, and tax exemption application, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, letters, and substantiation of taxes for the Near East Dance Foundation, 1971-1973 (1 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, letters, and substantiation of taxes for the Near East Dance Foundation, 1971-1973 (2 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, letters, and substantiation of taxes for the Near East Dance Foundation, 1971-1973 (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Letter concerning the status of pending actions against the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and consent forms granting Powers of Attorney from Doris Duke to others, 1969–1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and associated documentation regarding acquisition of the Wetmore property in Newport, RI, 1970–1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence concerning litigation of Romano vs. Duke, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lease of property on Hanua Street, Ewa, Hawaii, for the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture (SEAAC), 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Various documentation regarding taxes for SEAAC, 1970–1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Sheriff’s Execution Against Property in the case of Doris Duke vs. Paris Theodore, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence regarding Newport, RI 1970–1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Letter regarding tax payment of $3,087.37 to the State of New Jersey - Department of the Treasury, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence primarily concerning financial, accounting, and tax matters, 1967–1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence pertaining to the Tax Reform Act of 1969. Includes information for the Newport Restoration Foundation and Duke Gardens Foundation, 1969-1973 (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence pertaining to the Tax Reform Act of 1969. Includes information for the Newport Restoration Foundation and Duke Gardens Foundation, 1969-1973 (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence pertaining to the Tax Reform Act of 1969. Includes information for the Newport Restoration Foundation and Duke Gardens Foundation, 1969-1973 (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Documents concerning the accidental death of Eduardo Tirella in Newport, R.I., 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence concerning Doris Duke's traffic ticket in California, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence concerning the claim of Trask vs. Duke, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence regarding dispute over an alligator jacket and black organdie dress. Valentino is the designer, Fabius is the shipping company, and Ira Furman & Co. is the customs broker, 1969-1972 (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence regarding dispute over an alligator jacket and black organdie dress. Valentino is the designer, Fabius is the shipping company, and Ira Furman & Co. is the customs broker, 1969-1972 (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Change of Address Notifications, 1973–1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Documents pertaining to a surprise party for Leta McBean co-hosted by Doris Duke and Peter McBean, 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Documents pertaining to a surprise party for Leta McBean co-hosted by Doris Duke and Peter McBean, 1970 (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Doris Duke’s driver’s license renewal information and correspondence with Elise Cooper, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Financial statement for the 475 Park Avenue Corporation, New York, N.Y., 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report for Angier B. Duke Memorial, Inc., 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Invitations to events, 1970–1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report for Spouting Rock Beach Association, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and photographs of two Meissen boxes that Doris Duke offered to the Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements for Seventrees Holsters Ltd., 1967-1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Photographs – Grist Mill Additional Property, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)